By the way, a kiss Alma Garcia, a kiss
Por cierto un beso alma García un beso
because I'm not going to forget the
porque no voy a olvidar las
presenters who have said goodbye to
presentadoras que se han despedido de
us and those who I don't take into
nosotros y las que no lo tengo muy en
account very well, it's that I'm my daughter, let's
cuenta pues es que soy hija mía vamos a
see who is born, it's born, you can't
ver a quién le nace le nace no puede
blame anyone for anything, not for good or
reprocharle nada a nadie Ni para bien ni
for bad, I mean, why are you going to
para mal o sea por qué le vas a
blame someone? I don't wish you
reprochar a alguien que no te deseo
luck. I mean, no, without further ado, a wonderful
suerte O sea no sin más maravilloso
message, a kiss, Sonsoles,
mensaje de un beso sonsoles
very affectionate again, I don't have to be a
muy cariñoso otra vez no tengo que
person, Rosa, I'll keep it to myself, I'll keep it to myself. Well,
persona Rosa él me lo guardo me lo
nothing, keep it to yourself when another
guardo Pues nada guárdatelo cuando otro
program ends. Well, don't say goodbye to
programa acabe Pues tú no te despidas de
them, so there's no more, but
ellos así que no hay más pero es que
nobody has the obligation. I mean, the other way around,
nadie tiene la obligación O sea al revés
what's surprising is what
lo que sorprende es lo que ha hecho
Sonsoles has done, what's not surprising is that they
sonsoles lo que no sorprende es que no
are not presented by a presenter,
estén presentados por presentador
save me, no.
sálvame que no